--Download Movies and Tv shows from - www.msmoviesbd.com --
[please Bookmark our website]
Nor for the pestilence
that walketh in darkness.
Nor for the destruction
that wasteth at noonday.
Be with me Lord,
in my hour of need.
Because thou hast
made the Lord,
which is my refuge,
even the most high,
thy habitation.
[people] Be with me Lord,
in my hour of need.
[Ed] There shall
no evil befall thee,
neither shall any plague
come nigh thy dwelling.
[people] Be with me Lord,
in my hour of need.
[Ed] For he shall give
his angels charge over thee,
to keep thee in all thy ways.
[people] Be with me Lord,
in my hour of need.
Let's take a little break,
shall we?
Hon, are you feeling
all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[sighs]
I just can't remember
one quite like this.
He should try and get
some sleep.
Yeah. Here you go.
-Oh, I'll take him,
Mr. Glatzel.
-Huh?
Yeah.
Thank you.
-Thank you, Arne.
-No problem. Come on, buddy.
He can't take much more
of this.
He won't have to.
Things will move quickly
now that the exorcism's
been approved.
Father Gordon's already
on his way.
You're one brave kid,
you know?
I was a little runt growing up,
so I know what it's like
to be picked on.
But...
But that was nothing compared
to what you're going through.
I don't feel very brave.
Being brave doesn't mean
you're not scared.
It means you are scared
but you hang in there.
It's gonna be all right.
I won't let anything
happen to you.
I promise.
Arne. When are you gonna
ask my sister to marry you?
[chuckles]
I don't know what
you're talking about.
-Come on.
-No, I don't, I...
-[knock on door]
-[gasps]
[loud banging on door]
-[loud bang]
-[door knob rattling]
[rattling stops]
[rustling softly]
[knife unsheathes]
[breath trembling]
[tap knobs squeaking]
No! Help me!
No, no, no! No, no, no!
[screaming]
-David!
-[Judy] David! Where is he?
[glass breaking]
David!
[David screaming]
[breathing heavily]
[Carl] What's happening, buddy?
Are you okay?
David, what's going on?
David?
[yelling]
[screaming]
[Carl] No!
Father, we need to do this,
right now!
Okay, let's get him down
to the car and we'll drive him
to the church.
No, Father. Right now.
[David screaming]
[grunts] No! No! No!
[yells]
Grab his arms, don't let go.
[screaming]
Save your servant
who trusts in you, my God.
Let him find in you, Lord,
a fortified tower in the face
of the enemy.
Put on the full armor of God,
that ye may be able to stand
against the wiles of the devil.
Against the powers
of the darkness of this world.
Against wickedness.
[gasps]
-[groans]
-Lorraine, what's wrong?
I'm fine.
Lorraine.
Lord! Send him aid
from your Holy place
and watch over him from Sion.
-[sizzling]
-[screaming]
Lord, heed my prayer.
Lord!
[distorted scream]
[screaming stops]
[rumbling]
[distorted laughter]
No. Father!
[Debbie shrieks]
[Lorraine] Father!
-Where's your first aid kit?
-It's in the kitchen!
I'm on it!
Ed, hurry up!
Hurry, Ed!
Ed. Ed, Hurry!
[reciting in Latin]
[distorted laughter]
It's not working!
[continues reciting in Latin]
[bones cracking]
What? David, wait!
Stop it! What? What?
-[yells]
-[screaming]
David! David! Help me, please!
What are you doing? David!
Help him, please!
David, stop it! David! David!
[screaming]
-Leave him alone!
-Arne, don't talk to it.
I said, leave him alone.
He's just a little boy,
you coward!
No, Arne, don't talk to it!
[Debbie screams]
[distorted] I'll stop
your heart, old man.
[gasping]
Ed!
[groans]
Hey!
Listen to me. Look at me.
[screams]
Look at me. I know
you're still in there, David.
Just leave him alone, okay?
Leave him alone and take me.
Take me.
-[gasping]
-Hey, take me. Take me!
David!
Leave him alone and take me!
[breathing heavily]
[gasps]
No.
No, no.
David. David, David!
David, are you okay? Hey, hey.
David, go with Mom.
Oh, oh!
Yes, David.
[gasping]
Ed? Ed! Hon!
What?
[groaning]
-Somebody call 911!
-Okay.
Mrs. Warren.
He's stabilized.
We're gonna transfer him
to the coronary unit.
-So, it was a heart attack?
-Yes.
And not a minor one,
I'm afraid.
-Can we see him now?
-Not yet.
We're gonna to put a stent
into his artery,
try to get blood flowing
back to his heart.
[exhales]
So, is he gonna be all right?
We're gonna need to run
a few more tests before
I'm comfortable answering that.
I'm sorry.
-[Arne] Leave him alone!
-[Ed] Arne, don't talk to it.
Leave him alone and take me.
Leave him alone!
[David screaming]
[machine whirring]
[whirring stops]
Hey, the mummy lives.
Hey, why did you let me
sleep so late?
I didn't let you,
I couldn't wake you.
-You couldn't wake me?
-No, I couldn't.
Oh, that's strange.
You mustn't have been
trying very hard.
[Debbie] No.
[dogs barking]
-[man] Buddy! Easy, easy, easy!
-Okay, Bruno is right outside.
Oh, come on.
Bruno's a worldly man,
he doesn't care.
[laughs] No.
No, no, wait. Actually,
I do want to ask you something.
Okay. What do you want
to ask me?
Um...
-It's no big deal.
-Mmm-hmm.
-I've... I've been thinking...
And now David's
out of the woods,
maybe we should
put all this behind us
and get out of this place.
-You know?
-You mean, leave Brookfield?
Sure, why not?
We've got nothing keeping
us here now. Do we?
Oh, yeah.
Nothing but my family
and all the money
we don't have. Arne--
Okay, well,
money's no big deal, right?
We're both working,
and this place doesn't
cost us anything.
Arne, I just started this job.
I can't just up
and walk out now.
-[Bruno] Jesus Christ!
-And besides,
Bruno doesn't know
the first thing about
taking care of these dogs.
Hey...
Let me think about it. Okay?
-You'll think about it?
-Yeah, I'll think about it.
Okay. There we go.
Okay, get dressed.
I love you.
-[rock music playing]
-I think David will love that.
-Did you call my mom?
-[Arne] Yeah, I did.
-I told her we were going
to be very late.
-Okay, thank you.
No, Arne. Please stop eating,
please stop.
Mrs. Haskett,
so good to see you,
thanks for coming by.
-Hey, we're headed out now.
-Bye, Pookie.
I wrote down a list of stuff
for you to do
while we're gone.
Oh, keeping track of this stuff
is what I'm supposed to be
paying you for.
Not on weekends, you're not.
I'm letting you live here
rent free.
That should buy me the weekends
maybe the holidays, too.
Okay, Andy gets one cup,
everyone else gets two.
Magic and Sparky are getting
picked up, so you don't need
to worry about them.
But, you'll have to take
everyone else outside at some
point this afternoon.
Oh, Ruby's allergic to bees,
if she gets stung you've got
to call the emergency vet.
I wrote the number down
and stuck it on the fridge.
[song faltering]
Yo, Arne, you wanna make
a quick five bucks, man?
My stereo's busted.
Yeah, sure.
I'll take a look at it later.
But, make it 15.
Ten.
-...what happened this morning.
-I know.
Ma, okay.
Please don't say anything.
I won't say anything,
I promise.
Okay, just...
He asked if we could
leave Brookfield.
-[gasps] You know what
that means, don't you?
-No.
-Actually, you mean
he proposed?
-Not exactly.
-Did you say, yes?
Arne! Can you bring out
the tray with the meat on it?
Oh, yes. I'm starving!
Are you starving, bud?
Yeah.
Okay, I'll go get the meat.
-Ow!
-[chuckles]
[rustling]
[squeaks]
[screaming]
[gasping]
[panting]
[woman on PA]
Doctor Merrick, to OR-6.
[knocks on wood]
It was nice seeing Judy again.
Will she be staying long?
I don't know, um,
it depends if...
The nurse says that you
have been sleeping
in that chair.
Ed would understand if you went
home for a little while.
Did I ever tell you the story
of how we met?
No, I don't think so.
Just that you were young.
In high school, wasn't it?
Yeah. We were 17.
I went out with
my girlfriends and...
And he was an usher
at the movie theater
that we went to.
Afterwards...
we went out for ice cream.
He took me out to the park,
but then it started to rain.
And we stood under the gazebo
until it stopped.
That was 30 years ago.
I could go back
to the house, Father,
but my home is here
with him.
[indistinct chatter]
[sputtering]
[buzzing]
Jesus Christ, Arne!
What the hell?
[breathing heavily]
Can we please do something
about this racket?
These dogs are driving
me crazy!
[Debbie] They probably just
smell a rabbit or something.
-How come you're not at work?
-I wasn't feeling so hot.
[laughs] Arne!
Perfect timing, man.
[dogs barking]
Hey, why don't you come inside
with me, have a beer.
If we get that stereo fixed
we can put up a sign,
close up shop.
-You know what,
I don't think so, Bruno.
-Come on.
-Why, you quit drinking?
-No, I just don't--
Tell you what, we can
both quit next Saturday.
How about that? [laughs]
[weakly] Lorraine. Lorraine.
-Lorraine.
-Daddy!
Oh, Ed, thank God.
Lorraine.
-You have to call the Glatzels.
-She just called, you're fine--
We have to warn them,
it's got the kid.
No, it's fine, it's over.
David is safe,
the demon is gone.
Arne. It's got Arne!
[rock music playing]
It's beautiful, man.
Nicely done!
Come on, man,
don't make me drink alone.
Your girl's gonna think
I'm a drunk.
Do you know...
that I saw these guys
play in Sydney?
They nearly blew the roof off
Her Majesty's Theater!
Bruno! Can you turn that down?
I'm testing out his work!
[volume increases]
[phone ringing]
[muffled music playing]
[breathing unsteadily]
Hey.
What's the matter?
Are you okay? Bruno--
-Let's dance, brother!
-Bruno! No, stop!
Bruno. Bruno! Oh, my Lord...
Okay. Bruno, go night-night.
-No! Not until we dance.
-Yes! No, we're not dancing.
-One dance! One dance!
-I don't want to dance! Bruno!
Okay, one dance.
[laughing]
[phone ringing]
-This is Officer Thomas.
-My name is Lorraine Warren.
I know how this is
going to sound,
but there's going to be
a tragedy at the
Brookfield Boarding Kennels.
[Debbie screaming]
Debbie!
[screams]
-Arne...
-Bruno?
No, stop.
Arne!
Bruno, stop!
Arne, help me.
-[roars]
-[screaming]
Arne, whoa. What is going on?
-What are you doing?
-[Arne yelling]
Arne, please stop it!
[dogs barking]
Baby?
-[music continues playing]
-What the hell?
[music stops]
[growling]
[yells]
[Arne grunting]
[Debbie] No, stop!
[sirens wails]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Hey.
You okay there?
You okay?
Now, you just stay
right there, okay?
Don't move.
I think I hurt someone.
This is Sergeant Thomas.
I have one victim down,
multiple stab wounds.
[reporter]
Residents of Brookfield
were shocked this afternoon
by the broad daylight murder
of Bruno Sauls.
Sauls, the manager
of a local dog kennel,
was stabbed 22 times.
This is the first murder in
that town's 193-year history.
[Arne] Who shall ascend
into the hill of the Lord?
Or who shall stand
in his holy place?
He that hath clean hands,
and a pure heart,
who hath not lifted up
his soul unto vanity,
nor sworn deceitfully.
He shall receive the blessing
from the Lord,
and righteousness from the God
of his salvation.
[Ed] Right. That's enough.
Thank you.
Well?
These religious objects
would've been enough
to provoke an inhuman spirit,
if there was one present.
Does that mean
he's not possessed?
The fact that he can read
from the Bible just seals it.
So, what does this mean,
then...
I'm just crazy?
Well... you're not possessed.
But that doesn't mean
that you weren't.
I... invited this
thing into me,
and that's the reason
that he's dead.
So, you know,
whatever happens to me,
I've got it coming.
No, you don't.
Look...
I was there.
Whatever is going on...
whatever happened that day...
that was not Arne.
We're going to help you
in every way that we can.
If the demon's gone,
what can you do now?
Who's your lawyer?
He was found covered
in the victim's blood.
The murder weapon
belongs to him and it's got
his fingerprints all over it.
Nobody's disputing any of that.
Arne knows that he's going
to prison.
All we're saying
is that there were
mitigating circumstances.
Mitigating circumstances?
Look, I don't think
he should get
the death sentence, either.
But I am not going
before a grand jury
and saying he was possessed
by demons.
It's never been done.
Yes it has! It's been done
twice in England.
The Michael Taylor case
was just a few years ago.
Let me rephrase that.
It's never been done
successfully.
Then let us help you.
Ed and I have proven
the existence of the demonic
hundreds of times.
You've proven it to the church.
This is a court of law.
The standards of evidence
are completely different.
The courts accepts
the existence of God
every time a witness swears
to tell the truth.
I think it's about time
they accept the existence
of the devil.
How are you going
to convince a jury
if you can't even convince me?
I'll tell you what.
You come over to our house
for dinner.
We'll show you the evidence
we've collected over the years.
Introduce you to Annabelle.
If you're not convinced,
we'll butt out.
Deal?
All right.
Show me what you got.
[gavel banging]
Mr. Johnson,
to count one of indictment
number S-A-J-1-2-1-6,
which charges you with
first-degree murder,
a class-A felony,
how do you plead?
Your Honor,
my client pleads not guilty
by reason of
demonic possession.
[bell tolling]
This is ridiculous.
I can walk down
a flight of stairs.
Oh, hush. You shouldn't
even be out of bed.
Lorraine.
I just talked
to a friend of mine
in the prosecutor's office.
He's gonna go for
the death penalty.
I'll build the case,
but that kid is gonna
either live or die
depending on what you two find.
Well, we won't let him down.
[lawyer] I hope not.
Keep me posted.
So, what now?
We've never had to prove
a possession after the fact.
Demons don't just
disappear like this.
There's something else
going on here,
something that we missed
the first time.
Where do we start?
At the beginning.
[Ed on tape]
It's July 18th, 1981.
This is Ed Warren,
here with Lorraine...
and Judy Glatzel,
Deborah Glatzel,
David Glatzel
and Arne Johnson.
All right, let's get started.
Who was there
when David first started
exhibiting this behavior?
[Judy] We all were.
It was the day we moved in.
There you go.
Go have fun with them.
-Wanna order some pizza?
-[Debbie] Yeah sure,
I'll do that right now.
-Hey.
-[Arne] Put that box down
a second.
-[Debbie] Why?
-I just...
What are you doing?
-Have a look...
-What is... Arne!
You know you're supposed
to do this when you
get married?
Okay, so maybe
we'll do that too.
[Debbie] Oh.
[Debbie shrieks]
[hinges creaking]
[screaming]
No!
Mom!
[breath trembling]
[David] I didn't know
what happened.
It was like a dream.
And nobody believed me
when I told them.
But that was the first time
I saw it.
I don't get it.
How could he have invited
a demon? He was only in here
for a few minutes.
There wasn't even anything
in here.
Where was the water bed?
Where that rug is.
The wood got damaged
when the mattress ruptured.
-Mind if I have a look?
-Please.
[gasps softly]
That's not water damage.
Hon, will you let me
handle this?
You're going to ruin your dress
if you go in there.
So, um, the guest room's
about 15 feet in
and to the right.
Okay.
-Just be careful.
-Just hold my purse.
[rustling]
-[rat screeches]
-[screams]
Lorraine! Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine, Ed.
It's just a rat.
[sighs]
[rats squeaking]
[praying in Latin]
[Lorraine]
It's a witch's totem,
used by Satanists
in their rituals.
Remember how I told you
that an inhuman spirit
needs to be invited?
And you couldn't imagine
how David could do that?
Well, you were right,
he didn't.
We think David was cursed.
And on the night
of the exorcism,
the curse was passed
from David into Arne.
Cursed?
Are you saying someone
did this to us... on purpose?
We've heard of
satanic rituals like this.
The demon is summoned,
the possessed individual
takes a life
and the demon departs.
Which is why Arne
was able to read
from the Bible afterwards.
Yeah. We think whoever
cursed David, used this
to draw the demon.
And we'd like you to start
mailing these out
to every police department
you can find.
Start locally.
And, just find out if they've
ever seen anything like this.
There might be someone else
we can ask about this.
Do you remember the priest
who helped expose the
Disciples of the Ram cult?
It would've been about
10 or 12 years ago--
-Father Kastner?
-Yeah, you're right.
Only it isn't "Father" anymore,
he's been retired for a while.
He tried to help those people.
He tried to understand
why they did what they did.
If anyone is going to be able
to tell us what this is,
it's him.
[Ed] Father Kastner.
I didn't hear the car drive in.
Would either of you care
for an omelet?
We had breakfast before
we left home.
I'm Ed Warren,
this is my wife Lorraine.
I have chicken shit
on my hands.
[both chuckle]
[Lorraine] Thank you.
Forget you ever saw this.
You've seen it before?
No. But I've seen ones like it.
This is sophisticated.
It's a very nasty piece
of work.
What I don't understand is...
is why?
David, the little boy
who was possessed,
he didn't do anything wrong.
Why would someone
target this family?
Why?
The "why" is irrelevant.
The "why" is counter
to everything that
the Satanist stands for.
His sole aim is chaos.
His nectar is despair.
But someone had to
put it under their house.
So, what does this tell you
about the person who made it?
Come with me.
[keys jangling]
I don't want to go down there.
[door opens]
What is this?
It's the reason you're here.
[door creaks]
I collected these
while I was studying
the Disciples of the Ram.
-You should burn all this.
-I've thought of it.
But I felt it was safer
to keep them locked.
I like taking guns
off the streets.
I don't suppose you have
all these books organized
using the Dewey Decimal System,
do you?
No. No. No, I do not.
The clues you seek could
be anywhere. Or, they...
Or, they may not be here
at all.
Ed, don't.
[Kastner] I studied
these people for nine years.
They worshipped
Satan and his demons
with blood sacrifice.
They defiled holy land
with their obscene rituals,
and they committed
acts of blasphemy...
which I shall never speak of.
But... these acts gave
them power.
The trial of the Disciples,
the lead prosecutor,
his wife was pregnant.
A few days after the Disciples
were all found guilty,
his baby was born
six weeks early,
with its heart
outside of its body.
Three months later,
his wife committed suicide
by laying her neck
on a railroad track.
A master Satanist
is not an adversary
to be taken lightly.
We know the dangers,
better than you might think.
This boy, who's headed
to the death chamber...
is saving him worth
everything you have?
Because that's what it may
very well cost.
[water dripping]
[clattering]
[mic feedback]
So, you gonna clean it up,
or what?
I'm sorry.
[loud thud]
[gasping]
What?
♪ Color me
your color, darling ♪
♪ I know who you are ♪
♪ Come up off
your color chart ♪
♪ I know where
you're coming from ♪
[chuckles softly]
♪ I know who you are ♪
[screaming]
[indistinct shouting]
It was here!
I swear to God, it was here!
[footsteps approaching]
Look what the Perron family
sent.
Oh, that was sweet of them.
[phone ringing]
-I got it.
-Ed, let me.
It's okay, it's okay,
it's okay.
-Hello?
- [Drew] Ed?
We've got a bite.
I just got off the phone
with a homicide detective
in Danvers,
he wants to talk to you guys.
He says he says he's seen it.
[door closes]
Katie Lincoln
and Jessica Strong went missing
about four months ago.
They were best friends
in high school.
Katie's body was found
near here, stabbed 22 times.
We still haven't found Jessica.
But when we searched her home
back in May...
we found this.
So, you're the experts.
What can you tell me
about this?
Well, to be honest, not much.
Only that if this totem works
the same way
as the one in Brookfield,
it's possible that
your missing girl
was possessed.
Look, I've read all about
what you two think happened
in Brookfield.
But I'm only interested
in leads that are grounded
in reality.
Good. So are we.
We were actually hoping
there might be something
in this case file
that might help prove
Arne's story.
No, no, no.
I brought you here to help me,
not the other way around.
Now, we've been looking
for a link to some sort of
satanic cult ever since
we found that thing.
And these devil-worshippers,
they're just people.
Crazy, evil people,
but, people.
Maybe we can help each other.
We need to see your casefile...
and you need to find
the missing girl.
So, give us a chance.
-To do what exactly?
-To find Jessica.
We've been combing
through these forests for over
three months now, Mrs. Warren.
I can see things that
your people can't.
[sighs]
One of these is the knife used
on Katie Lincoln.
The others I just pulled
from the evidence locker.
And what? You want her to pick
out the murder weapon?
Mmm-hmm.
I'll take you out there,
but first I want to see
what she can do.
Absolutely not! My wife's gift
is not a sideshow attraction.
If she is what you say she is,
then this shouldn't be
a problem,
Mr. Warren. Right?
-No way! Forget it. We--
-It's this one.
["Suspicious Minds" playing]
♪ We're caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out... ♪
It was a one-in-three chance.
[chuckles softly]
This song's appropriate.
♪ Because I love you
too much, baby ♪
You know, I actually met
Elvis once.
-Oh, yeah?
-Mmm-hmm.
-Was that before
or after he died?
-Before...
and after.
♪ When you don't believe
a word I say? ♪
You missed a turn.
The spot where
you found Katie's body,
it was back that way.
♪ And we can't build
our dreams ♪
♪ On suspicious minds ♪
[Debbie] They're in Danvers,
right now.
If they can find some way to
connect what happened there
to what happened to you,
then...
You know, it's...
It's a pattern.
They might even find out
who did this.
Okay. Well, that sounds great,
right?
-It's great.
-Baby...
What's going on?
Nothing.
I'm fine,
I'm tired, you know--
Come on.
You're keeping something
from me.
Don't you think
I can tell that?
Look, I'm fine. Totally fine.
It's cold in here.
Yeah, right?
It's like, they're trying
to freeze us out,
or something.
I remember what it felt like.
You're always cold,
and you're never alone.
David, what are you
talking about?
That's why you can't sleep.
Because it's never quiet
in your head.
Sometimes you think something,
then you're not sure
if it was really you.
But now you're seeing it.
It's here with you.
And it's telling you
to do things.
Arne, what is it telling
you to do?
You sure you should be tromping
through the woods like this?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Then what are
you worried about?
Afraid she won't be
able to do it?
[Ed] No.
I'm afraid that she will.
Ed, something terrible
happened here.
[branches creaking]
-[rustling]
-[gasps]
[wood scraping]
[both laughing]
[Jessica] Katie, wait up.
Hey.
I got you something.
They were selling them
at the May Festival this year.
Your parents still dragging you
up there for that?
Every year, since I was six.
[both chuckle]
It's dumb, but,
I thought this was cool.
It reminded me of the ones
we made in high school.
Will you help me put it on?
Sure.
[panting]
[gasping]
[sobbing]
All right, that's enough.
Hon, that's enough.
That's enough! Come on!
[breathing heavily]
Katie? Katie? Oh, my God.
What did I do?
Hon, no!
Lorraine!
[sobbing]
[panting]
[Ed] Lorraine!
Lorraine.
Ed.
[screaming]
No!
[grunting]
[both sigh]
It's okay. I got you.
I got you.
[Lorraine panting]
She's down there.
Ed, she's down there.
[siren wailing]
[paramedic] Blood pressure's
a little high.
I'm gonna give you
a vasodilator.
It's a pill, you're gonna
put it under your tongue.
It'll open up
your blood vessels.
Yeah, I have those.
I left them at home.
[paramedic] Yeah, well,
I wouldn't do that
anymore if I were you.
Mind giving us a minute?
Recovery team found a body.
-Is it--
-We're not sure.
Look, I know what
it looks like.
But, I don't want any of this
getting out until we have
a positive ID
from the coroner.
You know, we dragged
this basin. Twice.
Had to pull teeth
to get it done
a third time.
We never would've done it
if it weren't for you.
I'm just glad we could help.
Let me know where
you're staying.
And I'll get that casefile
to you in the morning.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Oh, my God, I've been leaving
messages all day.
-What's wrong?
-It's Arne. It followed him!
You said this was over,
but now he's trapped in there
with this thing
and it's telling him
- to kill himself!
- Debbie.
Just calm down and listen
to me. I need you to call
the prison chaplain, um...
-Father Newman.
Tell him that
Arne needs to be put on
a 24-hour suicide watch!
He's got--
[static screech]
What? Hello?
What is this thing?
[thunderclap]
[thunder rumbling]
[keys jangling]
[lock clicking]
[man] Arne.
God gives everyone the right
to defend themselves.
[lock clicks]
[Lorraine] This demon...
it's not here of its own
free will. It was summoned.
That doesn't make me feel
any better.
That means, we know that this
is a curse,
and curses can be broken.
All right.
Then, how do we do that?
Back at the Glatzel house,
I touched David's hand
and I saw something.
I didn't know what it was then.
But I think that I was
connected to the person
who is responsible for this.
Ed, that body they found...
if it's Jessica,
if it's really her,
then that connection
could still be open.
There's gotta be another way.
[gasping]
Okay... okay.
Okay.
The Lord is my shepherd,
there is nothing I shall want.
He maketh me to lie down in
green pastures...
[knock on door]
[rattling]
There's nobody there.
We'll leave a note.
[door creaking]
[door closes]
[switch ticking]
Oh, boy.
Please be careful.
[whimpers]
[exhales]
Do you see anything?
No. There's nothing.
There's nothing here.
I'm not sensing it.
-Lorraine, what is it?
-The connection.
It's here.
[train horn blowing]
[train engine chugging]
[Ed] Do you see anything?
Yes.
Yes, there are... some stairs.
I heard a train.
But now...
there's an altar.
All those black candles.
There's 12 of them.
In a circle.
Oh, Ed.
Okay, that's enough,
come back.
I can't.
Lorraine.
[switch ticking]
It's a woman.
[Ed] Can you see her?
[Lorraine] I am her.
Can you tell where she is?
I don't know. I...
[exhales]
She's doing it again.
She's reaching out to Arne.
She's trying to complete
the curse.
[gasps]
Oh, she has him.
She has Arne.
Oh, no, no.
No, no. Oh, God.
End this black sabbath.
By the blood of Calvary
I command it!
I got a cutter! C-19!
Come on, kid.
[wind blowing]
How are you doing this?
God has shown you to me.
Then your God has damned you.
Ed. The connection
works both ways.
[ticking stops]
[switch ticking]
Lorraine.
You need to come back.
-Lorr--
-[bones cracking]
Lorraine?
You need to break
the connection.
Drop her hand.
Lorraine, let go of her hand.
[gasps]
[growls]
[Lorraine gasps]
[both breathing heavily]
Ed...
She knows who we are.
[thunder rumbling]
[sighs in relief]
[Lorraine] We are so sorry.
[crying]
Oh, we're so sorry.
How's Arne?
He'll be all right.
They got him sedated.
We got the casefile.
There's got to be something
here that connects these girls
back to him.
That's great.
I got something
to show you, too.
I found it in the Stregheria.
It's early Renaissance.
The Church used it to identify
and persecute witchcraft.
Now...
my Latin is rusty, but...
I think this...
is talking about
a human sacrifice.
One by murder
and the other by suicide.
Does it say how to stop it?
Yeah, it looks like...
you can break the curse
by destroying the altar
it was cast from.
But...
this part looks like Aramaic.
This next part,
I can't read it.
But you stopped her.
Maybe she'll give up now.
She can't.
Once started, the curse
must be completed.
Her soul depends on it.
We'll find another way.
Was there anything
in your vision
that might help us
find her altar?
It was cold.
There was water dripping
from the ceiling.
I think I heard a train.
But it sounded strange somehow.
Like, um...
I don't know, muffled?
Well, maybe it was underground.
Could be. I don't know where.
This woman targeted
David and Jessica.
Maybe there's
a connection there.
Let me take a look at the...
Take a look at the...
file.
[thunder rumbling]
[groans softy]
Lorraine?
[leaves rustling]
Lorraine!
[breathing heavily]
[indistinct clatter]
Where is she?
You know, the two of you have
gathered quite the collection.
If you hurt her...
Oh, don't worry, Mr. Warren.
You're so close.
I'd hate for you
to give up now.
[loud thud]
[thudding]
[door creaking]
[growls]
-[roars]
-He who calls forth
the water of the sea!
The Lord of Hosts is His name!
Deliver Thy servant
from all the workings
of unclean spirits!
Fear and flee, unclean spirit!
-Ed!
-[breathing heavily]
Ed.
I'm sorry.
Ed, it was her!
It was her.
-[Drew] Ed,
what the hell is going on?
-Help me find it!
Find what?
[Ed] Where is it?
[Drew] Ed.
Ed!
She was here!
She was in our house!
When did these get here?
They just arrived yesterday
while you guys
were driving home.
They were fresh
when they got here.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[Lorraine] We have
to find this woman.
We've identified the curse
and now we have
Jessica's casefile.
There has to be
something in here.
Okay, I'm gonna take the book
to be translated.
There has to be a clue
about where we can
find the altar.
[Debbie] So what do we do?
You should go be with Arne.
He's gonna need you tonight
more than ever.
Ask Father Newman for help.
Drew, you and me are gonna
tear into those files.
We've got to find a link
between these cases.
And a Satanist's power
is strongest at night. So...
Let's hope she doesn't
try anything before then.
They've stopped his sedation.
He'll be coming around soon.
[Drew] There's nothing
in these interviews.
Her friends barely saw her
after she got back
from college.
Didn't that
seem strange to you?
I mean, we're here,
the Glatzels live here,
just 15 minutes away.
But Jessica lived
180 miles from here.
Why is this one so far away?
Hey, where did Jessica
find her totem?
I just saw something
about that.
It was in an interview
with her parents.
It was in a box.
"She brought it back home
in a box from college."
Where'd she go to college?
Fairfield.
This woman lives in the area.
Still a lot of ground to cover.
Yeah, but not
a lot of train tracks.
Remember Lorraine's vision?
She said she heard a train.
What time was it?
Maybe we can start
eliminating some of these.
[Ed] Probably
close to midnight.
[Drew] Then it can't be
either of these two.
The commuter lines
don't run that late.
That just leaves
this freight line
that crosses the river here.
The river.
Oh, dear God.
Mrs. Warren.
I'm sorry, Father,
we tried calling,
but we couldn't reach you.
We were hoping you'd help us
translate a passage
from this book.
Of course. Come in.
Thank you.
Give me your keys.
You stay here, call the police.
[Drew] What do you want me
to tell them?
Anything,
just get 'em out there!
[door shuts]
[Kastner] It's the curse.
It says, the curse needs three
victims to be complete.
It refers to them as...
"The child, the lover
and the man of God."
The embodiment of God's work.
Purity, love, faith.
Has there been another?
It's Ed. It's my husband.
Last night we found a totem
in his office.
That is unfortunate.
Here, come with me.
There's something
I need to show you.
[floorboard creaking]
Father?
I've been here many years...
starting when I was a priest.
The church
used this mill for storage.
It's where they put the things
that they were afraid of.
Things they didn't understand.
You had a child?
Her mother died in childbirth.
The Church couldn't know.
So I raised her here,
in secret.
It was just the two of us.
Our happiness
filled this house.
I continued my studies
into the occult.
I wanted to protect her
from all this.
Instead I created
a fascination.
We must be careful
how our obsessions are passed
to our children.
"He who dwells in the shelter
of the most high
will rest in the shadow
of the Almighty.
I will say of the Lord,
'He is my refuge
and my fortress,
my God, in whom I trust.'"
It's just the wiring.
You know, state building.
[Arne] Debbie.
Arne.
What is it?
She's... she's close.
You knew?
We came to you for help
and you knew this whole time?
She's my daughter.
I couldn't...
I didn't want to see.
After all these years,
I thought she'd come back
to me again.
And now I know
the real reason she's here.
There are tunnels
under this land.
She would explore them
as a child.
Her altar must be down there.
It's the only thing
that can break her curse.
We need to destroy it.
[door creaking]
She's here.
[Kastner] Go.
I failed as a priest.
And I failed as a father.
Please, God,
don't let me fail--
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[footsteps approaching]
[Ed] Lorraine!
Lorraine!
[Lorraine in the distance] Ed!
Ed?
Ed!
Lorraine!
[grunts]
[grunting]
[Lorraine] Ed!
[screams]
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
[screams]
[Lorraine shrieks]
[grunting]
Look at me.
Open your eyes.
[shushing softly]
Look at me.
[whimpering] No!
Open your eyes and look at me.
Open up.
-[Lorraine screams]
-[grunts]
Lorraine!
Lorraine?
Ed!
[groaning]
[coughing]
Ed?
-[Ed grunting]
-[crashing]
[grunting]
[Arne screaming]
-It's happening.
-Now?
Now.
[praying in Latin]
[grunts]
-[Ed grunts]
-Ed, stop!
[shouts] Stop!
Ed, I'm begging you!
[Ed grunts]
Ed! Stop!
-[screams]
-[glass shattering]
[siren wailing]
[Arne screaming]
[bones cracking]
Arne!
Arne, please. It's okay.
Our Father who art in heaven
-hallowed be thy name...
-No, Arne. It's okay! Please!
...thy kingdom come,
thy will be done
-on earth as it is in heaven.
-Arne, it's okay!
[Lorraine] Stop this!
Ed, I'm begging you!
I'm begging you, remember me!
[breathing heavily] Stop!
[gasping]
[grunts]
Ed, stop! [screams]
[Lorraine whispers] Ed, please.
Remember me.
Oh, my God! Guards!
...and lead us not
into temptation
but deliver us from evil.
-For thine is the kingdom...
-Arne, it's okay.
-...the power and the glory...
-[roars inhumanly]
...now and forever, amen!
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed by thy name,
thy kingdom come,
thy will be done
-on earth as it is in heaven.
-No, Arne!
Arne? Arne, what are you doing?
[Father Newman
continues praying]
What are you doing? Stop it!
What are you doing?
Father Newman, help him!
Please... Guards!
Please! Stop it!
Please help him!
[Lorraine]
You're not gonna do this!
This is wrong and you know it!
[grunts]
Father Newman... No, no.
What's happening?
Please, Father, make it stop!
[screams]
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name,
thy kingdom come...
No, no, no! Arne, no!
Arne, stop, please! Stop it!
Don't do this, Arne,
I love you!
No...
And lead us
not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil!
[Lorraine panting]
-[grunts]
-[screams]
[panting]
Ed... Remember me.
She tried to
turn you against me.
Because, she thinks our love
is our weakness.
But it's not.
It's not.
It's our strength.
Now, open your eyes.
Arne? Arne, are you okay?
Oh, my God! [cries]
Oh, my God.
[Ed grunts, pants]
Your curse is broken.
[bones cracking]
[groaning]
You promised a demon a soul.
-[grunts]
-[bones cracking]
And it can't go back to hell
without one.
Oh, my God.
It's okay. It's over.
Please say it's over...
[Ed grunting]
Hon... I...
I forgot my pills.
[breathing heavily]
[siren wailing]
["Brand New Day"
by Van Morrison playing]
♪ When all the dark clouds
Roll away ♪
♪ And the sun begins to shine ♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪ I see my freedom
From across the way... ♪
[Debbie] Arne?
Arne?
Excuse me. Arne!
I love you.
♪ And it gives so much light ♪
♪ And it comes
From the sky above ♪
♪ Make me feel so free ♪
♪ Make me feel like me ♪
♪ And lights my life
with love ♪
♪ And it seems like ♪
♪ Yes, it feels like... ♪
[bailiff]
Will the defendant please rise?
♪ And it seems like ♪
♪ Oh, yes, it feels like ♪
♪ A brand new day ♪
♪ A brand new day, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[Lorraine] Oh.
♪ And the sun shines down
All on the ground ♪
♪ Yeah and the grass
Is so green ♪
♪ And my heart is still
And I've got the will ♪
♪ And I don't really
feel so mean ♪
♪ Here it comes
Here it comes ♪
♪ Here it comes right now ♪
♪ And it comes
Right in on time ♪
♪ Well, it eases me... ♪
As we go back now,
listen to the tapes
as well as being there
and hearing him do it,
he would constantly challenge
what was in that boy.
What does that do
-to the whole system of law...
-[man] Yes.
...if a person
can walk in and say,
"The devil made me do it"?
[Lorraine] David, I'm going to
put this on you.
[Ed] In the name of Jesus,
Jesus repels you.
Leave this child alone.
It's on your forehead.
Yes, remember, you are
not strong, you're weak.
You're weak.
Jesus loves this boy.
This is... this is His child.
[Judy] Wake him out of it.
Prop him up. Do something!
[Debbie] He won't get out of it
right now, Ma.
[Judy] Well he called me
names, you didn't do
nothing now!
[Debbie] Well, what do you
think we've been doing
all this time?
[Ed] In the name of
the Father and the Son
and the Holy Spirit, amen!
[Arne] You gotta hold him down.
He told me to.
Hold him on the ground.
[Judy] Mommy's here.
Mommy's here.
Come on, wake up.
Come on. Get up.
Come on, let's go.
Get out. Get out of my son.
Get out of my son. Come on.
Come on, son. Come on.
Get out. Get away from my son.
[David] Go on! No!
[Judy] I'm your mother!
[David] No, you're...
[laughs evilly]
[Judy] David. David. Wake up!
[Ed] Let the boy go.
[Lorraine] Look,
you need to hold him.
[Ed] In the name of the Father
and the Son
and of the Holy Spirit. Amen.
[Judy] Do something.
Sit him up.
- [Debbie] It won't work.
- [Arne] You can't
sit him up, he's...
[Debbie] It won't work.
[David] Mom, you're dead!
[laughs evilly]
[Judy] David!
Please, get up!
--Download Movies and Tv shows from - www.msmoviesbd.com --
[please Bookmark our website]
.
Thank You For Downloading..